with you today.
And um I think back to uh 1994
when I was uh baptized uh into the 7th
Day Adventist Church. I was actually
baptized by Pastor Abraham Jules.
And um
I was baptized at Kingsboro.
Um, I was introduced to Adventism
through Lebanon 7th Day Adventist
Church.
>> And
I remember, um, you know, I'll often
share in my testimony that
when I was first introduced to this
message, I was blown away. I was super
excited
>> about what I had learned. And that
excitement is still present with me
today.
>> I don't typically get to come back to
New York so often. So uh speaking at a
church where I was or in the area where
I was introduced to Adventism is a very
special
uh occasion for me.
But I think what makes the occasion
more special today is religious liberty
and we are living in a time that is hard
to believe.
I think we have, you know, often said,
hey, we know that these things are
coming, but some of us has kind of put
it off in the distant.
Or some of us have believed that it's
going to happen, but even though we
believed it was going to happen, we just
didn't see it quite happening the way
things are happening right now.
So I want you to understand that as I
speak to you today, it is with that
urgency.
We are living in some stormy times.
And
as the song just uh stated, Jesus
is a rock.
Jesus is he is our shelter in a time of
storm.
>> So I want to thank uh Elder Richmond and
uh Pastor Lewis, Dr. Martin, um
Elder Ashme for that introduction. I
want to thank you for inviting me to
share with you. And let's pray today
because I want to talk to you today
about the sermon I've entitled a false
Jesus.
A false Jesus. Let's pray. Heavenly
Father, please speak through me today.
Lord,
take these words you have given me
and Lord, bring them to life.
I pray this in Jesus name. [music]
Amen.
In the book of John
11 verse one, the Bible says, "Now a
certain man was sick named Lazarus."
Thank you. Thank you. A certain man
was sick named Lazarus of Bethany, the
town of Mary, and her sister Martha. It
was that Mary which anointed the Lord
with ointment and wiped his feet with
her hair, whose brother Lazarus was
sick.
Therefore his sister sent unto him,
saying, Lord, behold, he whom thou
lovest is sick. And when Jesus heard
that, he said, This sickness is not unto
death, but for the glory of God, that
the Son of God might be glorified
thereby. And how many of you know the
story?
Jesus delays for some time before
actually coming to the place where
Lazarus
has now been dead for 4 days. And I'm
going to pick up in verse 38. Jesus
therefore again groaning in himself
cometh to the grave. It was a cave and a
stone lay upon it. [snorts] Jesus said,
"Take away the stone."
Martha the sister of him that was dead
said unto him,"Lord, by this time he
stinkketh, for he has been dead 4 days."
Jesus saith unto her, "Set I not unto
thee, if thou wouldest believe that thou
should see the glory of God."
Then they took away the stone from the
place where the dead was laid. And Jesus
lifted up his eyes and said, "Father, I
thank thee that thou hast heard me. I
knew that thou hearest me always, but
because of the people that stand by.
I said it, that they may believe that
thou hast sent me."
And when he had thus spoken, he cried
with a loud voice, Lazarus, come forth.
And he that was dead came forth bound
hand and foot with grave clothes. And
his face was bound about with a napkin.
Jesus saith unto them,
"Loose him and what?
>> Let him go."
The glory of Jesus
that he was about to demonstrate
was in
setting
a captive free.
>> I I don't know if y'all caught that.
the glory that Jesus said that his
disciples would see.
A lot of us think the glory was in him
raising the dead. But I want you to
understand something that every time
Jesus does a miracle. It is not to to
show that he could do a miracle, but it
was to show something greater. Do you
remember when the man uh uh was uh the
the withered the man that could not get
up and walk and and Jesus said unto him,
"Son, your sins are forgiven." And then
the people said in their minds, "What?
Who can forgive sins but God only?" And
and and in their mind it was an
impossibility. So Jesus says, "Okay,
to demonstrate to you that when I just
said his sins are forgiven, something
actually happened, let me let me give
you an example.
Get up and walk."
And the man gets up and walks. Now I
want you to understand something. What
was the greater miracle?
>> See, we think the miracle was, "Wo, he
got up and walked." No, no, no, no, no,
no, no.
Jesus simply did that to demonstrate
that when he said, "Your sins are
forgiven you," something actually
transpired in heaven. Amen.
>> So he uses the physical to teach a
spiritual lesson. And so when we see
Lazarus coming up out of the grave, Laz
Lazarus being set free, the miracle
>> was not so much that Lazarus rose from
the dead, but that Jesus is able to set
the captive free. Amen.
>> So, so when we say set the captives
free, we mean we mean liberty.
>> Yeah.
>> Liberty. Jesus is all about liberty.
>> Amen.
>> Jesus desires to give us liberty and
especially everybody religious liberty.
>> Now I know your minds are like wait what
religious liberty? Yes. G the entire
gospel is about religious liberty.
Let let me show you in Luke 4:16. The
Bible says, "And he came to Naz Nazareth
where he had been brought up. And as his
custom was, he went into the synagogue
on the Sabbath day instead of for to
read. And there was delivered unto him
the book of the prophet Isaiah.
And [snorts] when he had opened the
book, he found the place where it was
written, "The spirit," y'all know this
verse, right? "The spirit [snorts] of
the Lord is upon me because he has
anointed me to preach the gospel to the
poor. He has sent me to heal the
brokenhearted, to preach deliverance to
the captives and recovering of sight to
the blind, to set at
>> liberty
them that are bruised to preach the
acceptable year of the Lord. And so what
I'm trying to demonstrate to you early
on in the sermon
is that the actual Jesus is one who
cares about the poor.
>> One who cares about the bruised.
>> One who cares about the brokenhearted.
>> One who cares about the blind.
>> One who cares about the captives with a
desired goal of setting the captives
free.
liberty.
>> That's the actual Jesus.
>> All right. So, if I were to say, "Hey,
Jesus, true or false?" And then I said,
"The real Jesus cares about people who
are suffering. The real Jesus cares
about people who are in poverty. The
real Jesus cares about people who are
captive in different ways, you would say
yes, that is a picture of
>> the real Jesus.
Jesus came
to give religious liberty.
In John 8:31, the Bible said, "Then
Jesus said to those Jews which believed
on him. If you continue in my word, then
are you my disciples indeed, and you
shall know the truth, and the truth
shall make you free." They answered him,
"We be Abraham's seed,
>> and we were never in bondage to any man.
How thou, how sayest thou, you shall be
made free?" Jesus said unto them,
"Verily, verily, I say unto you, who so
committeth sin is the servant of sin,
and the servant abideth not in the house
forever, but the son abideth forever. If
the son therefore shall make you free,
you shall be free indeed." I need you to
understand that the religious liberty of
Jesus is liberty from sin.
>> You I want you to understand how
important the message of religious
liberty is. Jesus has come to set us
free from the bondage of the old man,
>> the bondage of sin. He has come to say,
"Listen, I want to make you free in me.
I want to make you religiously free."
>> How many of you would like to be
religiously free?
>> And not only does he Jesus doesn't come
and say, "Hey, I'm going to force you to
experience my religious liberty." He
even gives you the choice.
>> He gives you the choice. The Bible says
in Matthew 15:16 24, "Then said Jesus
unto his disciples, if any man will come
after me, if any man will come after me,
if
any man will come after me, let him deny
himself and take up his cross and do
what? Follow me." Jesus's religious
liberty was liberty to choose him.
liberty to to choose him so that we we
could be free from sin.
>> However,
this Jesus was not appealing to many of
the religious leaders.
>> They weren't interested in the Jesus
that came for the poor, the Jesus that
came for the captive, the Jesus that
came for the blind. That's not what
moved them.
That's not the liberation
they were looking for.
>> Are are y'all with me?
>> They weren't looking for that kind of
freedom. In fact, in John 8:33, they
answered him and said, "We be Abraham's
seed, and we were never in bondage to
any man. How sayest thou, you shall be
made free." They were offended
>> that Jesus came offering them religious
liberty.
>> Are y'all following?
They were offended. Now, now they know
that they've been captive to Babylon and
to Me Persia. They know this. They are
know they know they're under the Roman
rule of thumb. So, what they're saying
is, listen, we are not concerned about
spiritual freedom. We are already free.
THE MESSIAH WE are looking for.
>> Are y'all following me?
The Messiah we are looking for
>> is to be of a different nature.
>> That's the one we're looking for.
>> They wanted a Jesus to deliver them from
something else.
And so you would think, right, that
after Jesus raises Lazarus from the
dead, you would think the next verse
would be something like how amazing,
like, you know, the people rejoiced and
and the leaders saw something great in
Jesus. But if you have a KJV Bible and
your Bible has subheadings,
the very next, now this is not in the
verse, but it's just the heading of the
very next section. And you want to know
what the heading is?
The plot to kill Jesus.
>> It's in the same chapter, you guys.
>> The plot to kill G. That's the those are
the very next words.
What an interesting turn.
>> Why does that come up next?
And so let let's see what happens. So we
left off in John 11:44. They Jesus says,
"Loose him and let him go." And then
verse 45. Then many of the Jews which
came to Mary and had seen the things
which Jesus did believed on him. But
some of them went their ways to the
Pharisees and told them the things Jesus
had done. You got to be pretty deceived.
You have to be pretty deceived to see a
miracle of that nature
and go away as a spy.
>> To report
on the on the negative things Jesus has
done.
And so the text says, the text says, uh
uh then gathered the chief priests and
the Pharisees a council and said, "What
do we for this man doeth many miracles?"
They're complaining about this. Watch
this. If we let him thus alone, all men
will believe on him, and the Romans
shall come and take away both our place
and nation.
I need you to understand that the
deliverance they were looking for, the
Messiah they were looking for, the Jesus
they were looking for was one who would
overthrow the ungodly Romans.
>> That's the Jesus that they wanted.
>> This Jesus that cared about the poor and
the blind and and and the suffering. No,
no, no, no, no, no. That that's not the
Jesus we need. We need a Jesus that's
going to defeat our political
>> enemies. We need a Jesus that's going to
defeat those ungodly,
uncristlike other people that don't
believe as we do.
>> Please understand, they say two things.
The Romans will come and take away both
our place and our nation. So their
concern was with place and nation. And
when you look this up, these are two
things they're talking about. The place
was in reference to their temple and the
nation, of course, Jerusalem. They were
concerned with church and state.
>> Yeah.
Mhm. [laughter]
>> The religious liberty they were
concerned about
>> was making sure that their church power
>> and state power would not be interfered
with.
>> Are you understanding?
>> A and the Jesus that is presently before
them doesn't seem to care about that.
That's right.
>> He's talking about healing their hearts
and they're like, "What?
>> That's not what we need." Look around.
Don't you see the wickedness that those
ungodly Romans are doing?
>> How can you claim to be the Messiah when
you're not ready to overthrow?
>> And set us in charge.
>> That's the liberty
>> we're looking for.
They wanted a Messiah who would make
Jerusalem great again. [clears throat]
[applause]
They wanted a Messiah
>> who would fulfill their desires for
power.
And so in John 11:49, one of them named
Caiaphas being the high priest that same
year said unto them, "You know nothing
at all, nor consider that it is
expedient for us that one man should die
for the people that the whole nation
perish not." I need you to understand
that what you're watching here in this
story is a movement that has put nation
above Jesus.
>> Are y'all following what I'm saying? I'm
focused on the story here. I'm talking
about the story.
>> In the story, you have a group of
people, a movement that has said nation
is the highest priority for us.
>> And any Messiah that that that attempts
to say, hey, it's not about nation. It's
about what's in here. Here is my
promised land. This is the land I want
to conquer.
>> Yes.
>> No. No. No. No. We don't want that kind
of Jesus.
So, so it is better, listen, it is
better to get rid of that Jesus
>> that the nation may be saved
>> in the name of God.
>> Their concern was to keep their temple,
>> was to keep their national status under
Rome
>> and to eliminate any threat to that
arrangement.
In other words, for them, liberty was we
get to have our church. Liberty was we
have our political power. And liberty
was getting rid of anything that gets in
the way of our power.
>> So, not everyone who says religious
liberty actually means religious
liberty.
>> So, the Bible says, listen to this,
verse 55. Then from that day forth they
took counsel together for to put him to
death.
>> They had to put to death the Jesus that
was loving
>> and meek
>> and humble
>> and empathetic
>> and merciful.
>> They couldn't have that Jesus going
around in the streets. They they
couldn't have that [snorts] Jesus
preaching that kind of a message. That
was a soft Jesus. You understand?
>> That was a Jesus who wasn't really aware
of of the real issues.
>> So, they've got to get rid of this Jesus
because this Jesus is concerned with
freedom from sin. And their concern was
freedom from their political
adversaries.
>> The Jesus of the Bible must be rejected
in order to maintain their religio
political power.
I'm talking about in the story
>> what's happening here. So
>> So they need help to do this. A and so
to do this, they're going to end up
calling on a man by the name of Judas.
Judas becomes the embodiment of the
religious leaders in Jesus's day. And
and the reason I'm pointing this out to
you is because I need you to understand
something that is very that is very
crucial to understand. Listen to this.
In Mark 14:10,
and Judas a Scariot, one of the 12 went
unto the chief priest to betray him unto
them. And when they heard it, they were
glad and promised to give him money. And
he sought how he might conveniently
betray him.
Conveniently.
>> Conveniently.
>> So it wasn't a outward, hey, I hate
Jesus and I want to betray him.
>> It was it was a lot different. Judas was
a disciple of Jesus.
A and what ends up happening is that
this disciple of Jesus betrays Jesus on
behalf of religio political power.
>> And I want you to watch how it happened.
Matthew 26:47. And while he spake, lo
Judas, one of the 12 came and with him a
great multitude with swords and staffs
from the chief priests and the elders of
the people.
Now he that betrayed him gave them a
sign,
saying, "Whomsoever I shall kiss, the
same is he, hold him fast."
And forth with he came to Jesus, and
said, "Hail, master," and kissed him.
And Jesus said unto him, "Friend,
wherefore art thou come?" Then came
they, and laid hands on Jesus, and took
him. I need you to understand here that
in this context, kiss is a sign of
friendship, of worship.
And I want you to understand, beloved,
that there is a Christianity today that
is kissing Jesus while betraying him.
>> Did you understand what I just said?
>> There is a type of Jesus, a type of
Christianity today that has gained
momentum in the last, it's really gained
momentum in the last few years, but it
is it is a type of Christianity that is
very Judasike. Yeah,
>> this Christianity is concerned with
power, but it will kiss Jesus.
>> Are you following me?
>> To look like, "Hey, Jesus, I'm all for
you."
>> But in reality, what I want,
>> in fact, you understand that Judas
really wanted Jesus to be that kind of
Jesus that, you know, was more like,
>> "Come on, man." You know, get in their
face. Like, tell them how it is. you
know, like we need to we need to we need
to put that government down. And really,
you know what I'm saying, Jesus?
And Jesus is like, "No."
And Judas wanted to force Jesus's hand.
>> Beloved, there's a Christianity that is
present today that is seeking to force
the hand of Jesus in our country.
And they are doing it with a kiss.
>> They are doing it with with praise
songs.
>> They're doing it with tears. They're
doing it with with PASSIONATE PREACHING,
BUT IT'S all a Judas-like kiss.
Judas becomes the embodiment of this
movement of religious leaders who want
to bind Jesus. Bind the Jesus that saves
from sin
and grants religious liberty to the soul
to replace that Jesus
with a false Jesus.
What do you mean, pastor?
After they have Jesus, Matthew 27:15,
now by that feast the governor was want
to release unto the people a prisoner
whom they would. And they had a notable
prisoner called Bar Abbas.
>> Bar Abbas.
>> Bar,
>> son of
>> Abba.
Father
speak.
>> So, so before the crowd there is Jesus,
son of the father, and then there is Bar
Abbos,
>> son of the father. There are two sons of
the father. Y'all not y'all
y'all
>> there ARE TWO SONS OF THE FATHER
STANDING BEFORE the people.
And the question now is which son of the
father do the people really want?
>> Now you're going to think I'm making
this up. So instead of telling you, I'm
going to read it. Mark 15:7. And there
was one named Barabus, which lay bound
and them that had made or bound with
them that had made insurrection
with him who had committed murder in the
ins. So this son of the father, this
Barabus was an insurrectionist.
And the people,
>> the people chose an insurrectionist
Jesus
>> OVER THE ACTUAL JESUS. NOW, I KNOW WHAT
you're saying. We're talking about the
story, right? And y'all look really
moved about this story. Like, what in
the world? That could never happen in
our days. And I, you know, I I get you
in the story. In the story, you would
think that the real Jesus
>> would have been so different from the
counterfeit. By the way, some accounts
have his name as Jesus Barabbus.
>> Some translations literally read Jesus
Barabus.
>> Jesus son of the father or Jesus son of
the father. Which son of the father are
you going to choose? Which son of the
father do you want? And the people did
not want THE SON OF THE father who was
they didn't want the son of the father
who cared about the poor.
>> Are y'all following me?
>> They didn't WANT THE SON OF THE FATHER
WHO CARED about the neglected.
>> THEY DIDN'T WANT THE SON OF THE FATHER
who cared about those who who may have
been otherred or were not like them.
>> YOU'RE NOT LIKE US. WORD.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE THE SAME BLOOD AS US. NO,
NO, NO. WE DON'T WANT THAT JESUS that is
about bringing everybody together. We
don't want that Jesus.
>> The Jesus we want is the insurrectionist
Jesus.
>> What a crazy story. What would you do if
we were in those times?
>> Hey, it would be okay. It would be a
frustrating time. Boy, I tell you, it's
a good thing that happened back then.
BECAUSE YOU WOULD JUST WANT TO SAY TO
THE PEOPLE, GUYS, LOOK, look at him.
>> Look at his past. How can you How can
you choose THAT JESUS OVER THAT JESUS?
>> COME ON Y'ALL. THIS IS SIMPLE.
>> But I need you to understand there was a
spell over the crowd.
>> You understand what I'm saying? Like to
us, you know, we're living in our time
and we know that we know better. But in
that time, you know, it was it was
literally a the devil had worked a spell
over the minds of the people and it was
almost like a moment of cultic action.
We want that, Jesus.
>> I know y'all are saying, "Woo, I'm glad
I was not there then.
I'm just talking about what's
>> And so the people exchange Jesus's.
>> They get rid of one and replace him with
another.
>> This is the one we've chosen.
And beloved, what I'm trying to say to
you today in plain words is that there
is a counterfeit Jesus running around
America right now.
>> It It is not
It is not the real Jesus.
>> That's right.
>> It is not the real Jesus. It is a
Barabus Jesus.
It is a Jesus who is more concerned with
with making America really nice.
[laughter]
>> It is a make America nice Jesus.
>> Make America nice. A make America
nicely. A man Jesus.
>> The man of Christ is here.
Lord.
>> And there are people, beloved, that do
not understand the difference
>> between the between Jesus Christ and man
Christy.
It is a crazy time to be alive, you
guys.
>> Because I can imagine being back in
those days and saying, you know, I may
have been in an audience and you know, I
pray that I wouldn't have been deceived,
but I'm just like I look back and I'm
going, how could you guys not see?
>> How could you not see? And and you know
what I begin to realize is that
they chose Barabus because there was
there was a Barabus in them
[clears throat]
>> that made Barabus appeal to them.
>> Do y'all catch what I'm saying?
>> Something about the true Jesus didn't
sit well with them.
>> Nah, you know. Oh, too close, man. You
want me to You want me to focus on me
and not the wicked people out there? No,
I don't want to focus on me. I want to
assume that I've got it all together.
So, let's focus on the people that are
not following you, God. Let's focus on
the people who are who are the atheists
and you know the the they're living the
alternative lifestyles and let's focus
on those because those are easy targets.
I can turn my attention
from here
>> instead of instead of demanding
righteousness here, I'll demand it
>> there.
>> And I can still look Christian doing it.
Okay.
>> So what happens? What happens when you
accept a Barabus Jesus over Jesus Jesus?
Then here's what happens. Jesus warned.
He said in John 16:2, "They shall put
you out of the synagogues." The time
cometh that whosoever kill you will
think they're doing it on behalf of
Jesus.
>> Will think they are doing God service.
So watch this. If I accept a Barabus
Jesus, then ultimately if that if that
Barabus Jesus says, "Hey, you know what?
This person ought to die because they're
not following me
>> and that person ought to die or that
person needs to be put in jail or that
person NEEDS TO BE X, Y, OR Z." THEN
WHAT happens is you joyously
>> do what Barabus Jesus says. Yeah.
>> And that's why Jesus said, "The time is
coming where they that kill you will
think they are doing God a service."
>> Beloved, we are living in amazing times.
>> In manuscript release uh volume 39 or
manuscript 30 uh 39 1894, Ellen White
says this, "The form Satan assumed in
Eden when leading our first parents to
transgress was a character to bewilder
and confuse the mind. He will work in
just as subtle a manner as we near the
end of earth's history. All his
deceiving power will be brought to bear
upon human subjects to complete the work
of deluding the human family. So
deceptive will be his working that the
people will do as they did in the days
of Christ. And when asked, "Whom shall I
release unto you?"
Christ or Barabus. The almost universal
cry will be Barabus. Barabus.
>> Y'all thought I was making that up.
>> Now, beloved, here's the thing.
We as 7th day Adventists have understood
this
>> for a long time.
>> 20, 30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 80 years ago, we
were saying, "Hey, this is going to
happen." And people were like, "Y'all
are crazy." Because something like that
could never happen in America.
>> That's what people would say. Yeah.
>> And for many of us, we'd kind of be
like, yeah, it is kind of strange to to
think about how we could ever get to the
place where that happens in America,
where actual religious liberty is going
to be under threat from people who claim
to believe in religious liberty.
>> Absolutely.
>> But yet here we are.
>> I'm going to tell you something that
disappoints me.
When I see secular newscasters
warning about Christian nationalism,
>> I'm just like, where is the voice of
Seventh Day Adventists?
>> They don't even know what they're
warning about.
>> They're warning. THEY DON'T EVEN GET THE
whole picture.
They don't even see where this thing is
actually going.
>> There is one voice on the planet alone
that can speak to what is going on and
what is coming.
>> And where is that voice?
>> For some of us,
>> maybe we've gotten caught up in this
Barabus Jesus.
For others of us, maybe we just don't
care. We just want to come to church and
h, you know, let's have fun. Oh, I just
need to get the, you know, the week was
rough. I just need I just need to come
to church and just h
God has called us to be watchmen
>> on the wall.
>> Where is our voice?
In in Revelation 13:11, the Bible speaks
of this beast that comes up out of the
earth with horns like a lamb, but speaks
like a dragon. That sounds like Judas to
me.
>> Do y'all get what I just said?
>> Whatever that power is, THAT IT SOUNDS
LIKE JUDAS. It sounds like worshiping
with a kiss.
>> Absolutely. And and I want you to note
something here because
if we ask ourselves
why is this beast described as having
the horns of a lamb and we go elsewhere
in the scripture to see what the what a
lamb represents. The lamb represents
>> Jesus.
>> And in fact in John 1:29 the Bible says
the next day John seeth Jesus coming
unto him and said behold the lamb of God
which what?
>> Takes away the sin of the world. So the
purpose of the lamb is to do what
everybody? take away the sin of the
world. Could the Bible be telling us
that this beast in Revelation 13:11,
which represents a nation that will
claim to have Christian values, could it
be telling us that this nation is going
to attempt to take away the sin of the
world?
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Hold on. Take away the sin of the
world.
>> That's right.
>> How?
Like a dragon,
>> a dragon uses force.
>> A dragon uses force. Remember Jesus
comes, the true lamb takes away sin in
the heart.
>> Let me say it this way.
>> The true lamb wants to write the law of
God in the heart.
>> This counterfeit beast wants to write
the law of God in the government.
Oh, no. Y'all didn't y'all didn't you
didn't catch that. Did y'all catch that?
>> Did y'all catch that?
This power is more interested in putting
the commandments in schools.
>> BUT WHEN WE TALK ABOUT PUTTING IT IN THE
HEART, OH NO, WE'RE not under the law.
>> That's That's not for me.
>> BUT IT'S FOR THEM.
>> It's for those wicked people.
Beloved, where is the voice
>> of the church? You understand? You
understand now that the three angels
messages given in Revelation chapter 14
is about religious liberty.
>> It is a religious liberty message.
It is the everlasting gospel which is
designed to grant us liberty, religious
liberty, so that I am now free to
actually worship Jesus.
>> Free from the old man.
>> Are you with me?
>> BUT IT IS also freedom from false belief
systems.
Which means the everlasting gospel at
the end of time is calling people to
freedom from Babylon.
>> Freedom from captivity.
>> And where is the voice of God's people?
>> Where is the voice of God's people?
>> It's like everywhere you look, there's
distraction. Some people have got caught
up in this false Jesus and other people
just don't care. Just
they're just concerned with, hey, I have
my Jesus and you know, let the world do
world's doing.
>> Beloved, God has called us as a people
for such a time as this.
And I need you to understand, beloved,
that God needs more than one person or
two people or five people or 10 people.
He needs all of us engaged.
>> And you're saying, "Well, how am I cuz I
don't know the message." Guys, get to
know the message.
>> Please understand the message.
A storm is coming, relentless in its
fury.
Are we prepared to meet it? You
understand, beloved,
>> you understand that that the Bible
speaks of 10 virgins
>> and that five were wise and five were
>> foolish. [snorts]
>> And that it was at midnight that a cry
went forth, the bridegroom cometh, go ye
out to meet him. And five of those
virgins woke up without
>> oily.
I need y'all to understand something.
And I I am I am getting ready to to wrap
this up.
>> But but what I'm about to share with
you, beloved, I need you to understand
because I'm speaking to you as a church.
Now, if if you do not understand this,
you will end up
>> worshiping a false Jesus.
>> I need you to understand this.
You see in Revelation 13 we are told
that this beast this power is going to
deceive the whole world and the whole
world is going to unite together
under this deception
and the question becomes how in the
world is that possible? How is the devil
going to get people from different
political factions, people from
different backgrounds and different
religions? How is the devil GOING TO GET
ALL of them
>> together on the same page?
>> And some people say, "Oh, it's going to
be climate change." No,
climate change is not going to lead an
atheist to go, "I think that I should go
to church on Sunday and worship Jesus."
No.
>> Are you understanding what I'm saying?
>> Climate change isn't going to do that.
>> Earthquakes aren't going to do that.
>> If the whole world comes together,
beloved, it will only be it will have to
be a miracle.
The text says, "He doeth great wonders,
so that he maketh fire come down from
heaven on earth in the sight of men, and
deceive them that don earth by the means
of those miracles."
>> May I talk to you about miracles in our
closing moments here.
>> Please, I need you to understand this.
Lean forward, wake up, pay attention.
Whatever you need to do, get this. You
may have never heard this before, but
you're about to hear it now. In
Revelation chapter 16, the Bible says,
"I saw three unclean spirits like frogs
come out of the mouth of the dragon and
out of the me mouth of the prophet uh
the false prophet and out of the mouth
of the beast." And these are miracles
are these are uh spirits which go forth
unto the whole world to gather them to
the great day of God Almighty.
What is it that's going to gather the
whole world together according to what I
just read?
Three unclean spirits like what?
>> Like frogs.
>> Why does the Bible use frogs?
>> Okay.
>> Okay. I'm hearing all kinds of answers.
Listen to me, you guys. Where else in
the Bible do you hear a story about
frogs?
>> Egypt. Very good. Egypt. Watch this.
Remember when Moses goes to Egypt, God
sends him and then you know Moses and
Aaron, the first thing they do is they
throw their rods down and then the
magicians what? They counterfeited that
miracle
>> and then they turned the water to blood.
That's the second plague. And what did
they do? They counterfeited that
miracle. And then they brought the
frauds upon the land. And what did the
magicians do? They counterfeited that
miracle. And then that was the last
miracle they could counterfeit. Meaning
you guys, the thing that brings the
whole world together, atheists, uh, uh,
agnostics, Muslims, Buddhists, Jews,
the thing that brings the whole world
together will be the last counterfeit
the devil will be able to pull off.
And the question is, what is the last
counterfeit that the devil will pull off
that will deceive the whole world?
I need y'all to understand something.
In Daniel 11:40,
there is given the description of this
power called the king of the north, whom
the Bible says when he comes, he's
coming like a whirlwind
with chariots
and ships.
>> He's coming like a whirlwind. And
[snorts] it is immediately after this
event that Michael stands up. So, we
know that whatever this event is, it is
the event that that says to Michael, all
right, it's time. It's over. It's done.
Now, there's going to be a time of
trouble, such as never was. So, if we're
asking ourselves, hey, what does the
whirlwind in the Bible point to? Most of
the times when you look at the whirlwind
in the Bible, you're going to see that
the whirlwind represents the coming of
Jesus.
>> It is when God comes.
>> God comes in a whirlwind. Elijah was
caught up in a whirlwind. Isaiah
65:66:15
literally says the Lord is coming
with a whirlwind
like a whirlwind with his chariots. Wow.
>> Could Daniel 11:40 be telling us that
the final counterfeit that brings the
whole world together is when Satan
appears as Jesus? In other words, false
Jesus. In other words, Barabus Jesus.
Now, I know what you're thinking. I know
what you're thinking, pastor. We got
this. Um, we know that when Satan comes,
his feet don't touch the ground.
We got it.
First of all, I need you to understand
something
that it is by means of the miracles
that the world creates the image of the
beast.
>> Meaning, many of us think that we're
going to get a Sunday law. We're waiting
for a Sunday law. And when we see the
Sunday law coming to pass, we'll know,
hey, it's time to get ready.
Beloved, what actually happens is that
Satan himself is the one that initiates
the Sunday law.
>> Okay, y'all are like, "Wait, what' you
just say now?" Listen to me, guys.
>> In his assumed disguise, he says, "I
have changed the Sabbath from from
Saturday to Sunday and commands the
whole world."
>> It is this miracle that why? Because for
listen for atheists seeing
>> is believing.
And when you see when the Muslim sees,
when the atheist sees, when the agnostic
sees, when the BUDDHIST SEES, WHEN
EVERYONE SEES, there will be no denying
it except for one group of people who
have never been caught up in false
Jesus.
>> Are you understanding me?
But what I need you to understand,
beloved, is that the text says that when
this when this being comes, he's coming
with chariots and with ships. I need you
to understand ships represent the sea.
Chariots.
[clears throat]
>> Do you know the Bible says when Jesus
comes again, he's coming with thousands
and thousands of
>> So what I need you to understand,
beloved, is that when Satan comes, he
doesn't come by himself.
He is coming with demons [music]
disguised as angels.
>> And now y'all are beginning to sweat.
Now y'all are like, "Oh, hold on. Wait a
minute. I thought I just had to remember
that Jesus feet don't touch the ground."
Beloved, I need you to understand that
the overwhelming majesty of this being's
appearance, that alone,
>> if you don't know what you believe now,
>> I want you to imagine if you're
struggling in the time of the footmen,
>> what will it be like when, remember
guys, all 10 virgins were caught off
guard.
Did y'all catch what I JUST SAID?
>> WE'RE GETTING READY TO WRAP this up,
GUYS. LISTEN CAREFULLY. ALL 10 virgins
were CALLED OF GOD. MEANING, ALL WERE
UNAWARE THAT THIS thing was coming.
>> And when they all woke up, you either
were ready or you were not ready.
And beloved, if ships point to the water
and the waters represent the deep, then
not only is Satan coming with demons
disguised as angels, but he's also
coming with demons THAT WILL BE
DISGUISED AS THOSE COMING UP FROM THE
DEEP.
>> MEANING, BELOVED, THAT WE WERE ALREADY
TOLD that Satan will at the end of time
will impersonate.
>> See, you thought it was like one
impersonation.
I saw my my great-grandmother at my at
the foot of my bed and I was like, "The
Lord rebuke you." And she left. All
right, Jesus, I'm ready. Translate me.
>> No, no, no, no, no. I want you to
imagine a world
where remember how the frogs were
everywhere.
>> Remember how the frogs were everywhere?
>> They were in the cupboards and in the
under the sheets. They were everywhere.
I need you to understand beloved that if
you don't know what you believe now when
the times are fairly
>> I need you to understand that when this
what Liy calls the overmastering
delusion comes upon the world if you are
if your feet are not firmly rooted now
how will you do
>> how will you do
>> a false Jesus is coming We have preached
about it. We have warned about it. But
beloved, the question is, are we ready
for it?
>> If we don't understand that Revelation
13:11, this beast that's that has a
horns of a lamb and speaks as a dragon.
Some people think that this dragon
speak, this dragon speak doesn't happen
till the future.
>> Failing to realize
that this beast has been speaking like a
dragon since its inception.
Amen.
>> Our pioneers taught this. Yes, there's
coming a greater speaking like a dragon
in the future. But from its very
inception,
Protestantism has been hypocrisy
>> in this country. And if we cannot
identify the dragon voice from the past,
we will not be able
to hear it
>> when it gets louder in the future.
we will slowly make our way to saying,
you know, this Barabus isn't really a
bad guy.
>> There's something about him that, you
know, I know he's rough around the
corners and,
>> you know, but there's something about
him that just
>> kind of gets, you know, I kind of I
didn't used to like him at first,
>> but now, you know, he's kind of kind of
growing on me.
Beloved, I want to make an appeal.
And this appeal is not an appeal to, you
know, you're here. And I'm trusting
you're here because you want to hear the
word of God.
>> My appeal to you today
is very simple. God needs your voice to
speak. Amen.
>> And if you're saying, "I can't speak."
He needs you
to fill your oil, your lamp with oil
to get that light burning again. If the
light went out because you're like,
"Man, this thing is taking too long."
Listen,
let me say it this way.
In Exodus 25, Moses goes up
out of a cloud receives him out of the
sight of the people as he goes up to
talk to God. Let me say that again. In
Exodus 25, Moses goes up to meet God and
he goes up in a cloud. I'll just say it
one more time. In Exodus 25, Moses goes
up to meet God and a cloud re a cloud.
Then Exodus 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 Moses
is still up in the mount. And in 32 the
people who had been saying yeah Jesus I
mean Moses is coming back again
>> began to get tired
>> and weary. IS HE REALLY COMING BACK?
>> And so THEY GET TO THE POINT WHERE
THEY'RE LIKE MAN THE MOSES DELAYTH his
coming. And so what do they do? They
build an image to a beast.
>> And and and after they build an image,
they say, "This is a feast unto the
Lord. We're going to worship Jesus this
morning."
>> Beloved, we are living in that time.
Jesus back in Acts chapter 2. In Acts
chapter 1, in in in the end of the
Gospels, the a cloud received him out of
the sight of the people. He is up in
heaven. And for MANY OF US, WE'RE LIKE,
"OH, our Lord delayeth his coming." In
the meanwhile, beloved, an image is
about to be built to the beast. And if
we are not like those Levites, y'all are
not feeling me.
>> You know, the ones that respons were
responsible for the sanctuary.
>> If we do not take our position
seriously, you guys, souls are going to
be lost. Maybe including our own.
If it's your desire today, say, "Lord,
I'm I need to stop playing,
get Lord, help me to get serious. Grant
me religious liberty so I could worship
you in spirit and in truth. And help me,
Lord, to use that religious liberty to
to equip my mind with the word of God
and equip my heart with the fire of God
and equip my mouth with the words to
speak so that I can share to my
neighbors, to my friends, to whoever
will listen. If that is you, I want you
to say, I want you to stand on your
feet. Say, Lord, that's me. [music]
That's me. Help me to become, help me to
experience religious liberty and help me
to be a preacher, a teacher, a sharer of
religious liberty.
Heavenly Father,
we are living
[music] in stupendous times.
It seems like there is hypnotism
happening all around us. [music] And the
prophet of the Lord literally told us
minds will be hypnotized
in the last days.
>> [music]
>> Lord, I pray that you would help us as a
people, as a [music] church
to lift our voices
>> in protest, in warning of what is coming
upon the world. Lord, there are other
voices warning and they don't even
understand the magnitude of what is
coming.
>> Lord, our voice is needed,
>> but our voice is absent.
The silence is stunning
for people who have talked about this
for decades.
The silence,
Lord, what a rebuke.
Please Lord, forgive us,
equip us,
set our hearts on fire.
And Lord, may we warn this world of what
is to come, but may we also be ready for
when [music] you come again. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen. And amen. You may be
seated.